14 Puig-Oriol Palau-solità i Plegamans, Barcelona 08184

(+34)652 28 07 98

aitor.garciamin@gmail.com

Porfolio

Skills

C# Unity C++ SDL2

Languages

Spanish

Catalan

English

Aitor Garcia Miñana

Gameplay Programmer

I'm a passionate game programmer with 4 years of game development experience with Unity and C++.

During my studies in a multimedia application developer vocational cycle at Escolas Pia of Granollers, I worked as an intern at VIoD Games Studio.

Besides game development, I'm passionate about playing video games, reading and watching TV shows.

Experience

Solo Game Developer

July 2019 - Present

Designing and development of video games and prototypes.

VIoD Games Studio - Intern programmer

April 2019 - July 2019

Trainee programmer in charge of implementing an endless wave mode in a VR game.

Education

DAM-VIoD Escola Pia Granollers - Multi Platform Application Development vocational cycle

September 2017 - June 2019